John H. Cornehlsen Papers 5730
Kheel Center for Labor-Management Documentation & Archives
- Series I: Psychological Profiles
  - Sub-Series B: Profiles done for Individuals
    - Individual Files: 1-O to 12-O (Box 42, Folder 29)
    - Individual Files: OB (Box 42, Folder 30)
    - Individual Files: OB (Box 42, Folder 31)
    - Individual Files: OB (Box 42, Folder 32)
    - Individual Files: OK (Box 42, Folder 33)
    - Individual Files: OR (Box 42, Folder 34)
    - Individual Files: Os (Box 42, Folder 35)
    - Individual Files: Ot (Box 42, Folder 36)
    - Individual Files: 1-P to 24-P (Box 42, Folder 37)
      Code: 1P-24P
    - Individual Files: 24-P to 48-P (Box 42, Folder 38)
      Code: 24P-48P
    - Individual Files: Pa (Box 42, Folder 39)
    - Individual Files: Pa (Box 42, Folder 40)
      Code: 20P
    - Individual Files: Pa, 1978 (Box 42, Folder 41)
    - Individual Files: Pa, 1955 (Box 42, Folder 42)
    - Individual Files: Pa, 1962 (Box 43, Folder 1)
    - Individual Files: Pe, 1955 (Box 43, Folder 2)
    - Individual Files: Pe, 1955 (Box 43, Folder 3)
    - Individual Files: Ro, 1970 (Box 43, Folder 4)
    - Individual Files: Pe, 1953 (Box 43, Folder 5)
    - Individual Files: Pe, 1953 (Box 43, Folder 6)
    - Individual Files: Pe (Box 43, Folder 7)
    - Individual Files: Pe (Box 43, Folder 8)
    - Individual Files: Pi, 1975 (Box 43, Folder 9)
    - Individual Files: Pi, 1957 (Box 43, Folder 10)
    - Individual Files: Po, 1976 (Box 43, Folder 11)
    - Individual Files: Pr (Box 43, Folder 12)
    - Individual Files: Qu (Box 43, Folder 13)
    - Individual Files: Qu, 1957 (Box 43, Folder 14)
      Code: 3Q
    - Individual Files: 3-R to 30-R (Box 43, Folder 15)
      Code: 3R-30R
    - Individual Files: 31-R to 61-R (Box 43, Folder 16)
      Code: 31R-61R
    - Individual Files: Ra, 1957 (Box 43, Folder 17)
    - Individual Files: Ra, 1956 (Box 43, Folder 18)
    - Individual Files: Ra, 1955 (Box 43, Folder 19)
    - Individual Files: Ra, 1970 (Box 43, Folder 20)
    - Individual Files: Re, 1962 (Box 43, Folder 21)
    - Individual Files: Re (Box 43, Folder 22)
    - Individual Files: Re, 1983 (Box 43, Folder 23)
    - Individual Files: Ri, 1976 (Box 43, Folder 24)
    - Individual Files: Ri, 1962 (Box 43, Folder 25)
    - Individual Files: Ro, 1956 (Box 43, Folder 26)
    - Individual Files: Ro, 1967 (Box 43, Folder 27)
    - Individual Files: Ro, 1964 (Box 43, Folder 28)
    - Individual Files: Ro (Box 43, Folder 29)
    - Individual Files: Ro, 1959 (Box 43, Folder 30)
    - Individual Files: Ro, 1966 (Box 43, Folder 31)
    - Individual Files: Ro (Box 43, Folder 32)
    - Individual Files: Ro, 1969 (Box 43, Folder 33)
    - Individual Files: Ro (Box 43, Folder 34)
    - Individual Files: Ro, 1954 (Box 43, Folder 35)
    - Individual Files: Ro, 1968 (Box 43, Folder 36)
    - Individual Files: Ru, 1963 (Box 43, Folder 37)
    - Individual Files: 1-S to 30-S (Box 43, Folder 38)
      Code: 1S-30S
    - Individual Files: 31-S to 60-S (Box 43, Folder 39)
      Code: 31S-60S
    - Individual Files: 61-S to 80-S (Box 44, Folder 1)
      Code: 61S-80S
    - Individual Files: 81-S to 122-S (Box 44, Folder 2)
      Code: 81S-122S
    - Individual Files: Sa, 1963 (Box 44, Folder 3)
    - Individual Files: Sa, 1967 (Box 44, Folder 4)
    - Individual Files: Sa, 1974 (Box 44, Folder 5)
    - Individual Files: Sa, 1966 (Box 44, Folder 6)
    - Individual Files: Sa (Box 44, Folder 7)
    - Individual Files: Sa, 1959 (Box 44, Folder 8)
    - Individual Files: Sc (Box 44, Folder 9)
    - Individual Files: Sc (Box 44, Folder 10)
    - Individual Files: Sc, 1954 (Box 44, Folder 11)
    - Individual Files: Sc (Box 44, Folder 12)
    - Individual Files: Sc, 1977-1978 (Box 44, Folder 13)
    - Individual Files: Sc, 1977 (Box 44, Folder 14)
    - Individual Files: Sc, 1977 (Box 44, Folder 15)
    - Individual Files: Se, 1966 (Box 44, Folder 16)
    - Individual Files: Se, 1968 (Box 44, Folder 17)
    - Individual Files: Sh, 1967 (Box 44, Folder 18)
    - Individual Files: Sh, 1962 (Box 44, Folder 19)
    - Individual Files: Sh (Box 44, Folder 20)
    - Individual Files: Si, 1962 (Box 44, Folder 21)
    - Individual Files: Si, 1958 (Box 44, Folder 22)
    - Individual Files: Si, 1960 (Box 44, Folder 23)
      Code: 77S
    - Individual Files: Si, 1981 (Box 44, Folder 24)
    - Individual Files: Sm, 1956 (Box 44, Folder 25)
    - Individual Files: Sm, 1966 (Box 44, Folder 26)
    - Individual Files: So (Box 44, Folder 27)
      Code: 117S
    - Individual Files: So, 1971 (Box 44, Folder 28)
    - Individual Files: So (Box 44, Folder 29)
    - Individual Files: St (Box 44, Folder 30)
    - Individual Files: St (Box 44, Folder 31)
    - Individual Files: St, 1971 (Box 44, Folder 32)
    - Individual Files: St, 1956 (Box 44, Folder 33)
      Code: 69S
    - Individual Files: St (Box 44, Folder 34)
    - Individual Files: St, 1964 (Box 44, Folder 35)
    - Individual Files: St (Box 44, Folder 36)
    - Individual Files: Su (Box 44, Folder 37)
    - Individual Files: Su (Box 44, Folder 38)
    - Individual Files: Sw, 1971 (Box 44, Folder 39)
    - Individual Files: 2-T to 41-T (Box 44, Folder 40)
    - Individual Files: Te, 1967 (Box 45, Folder 1)
    - Individual Files: Te, 1967 (Box 45, Folder 2)
    - Individual Files: Te, 1968 (Box 45, Folder 3)
    - Individual Files: Te, 1958 (Box 45, Folder 4)
    - Individual Files: Th (Box 45, Folder 5)
    - Individual Files: Ti (Box 45, Folder 6)
      Code: 21T
    - Individual Files: To (Box 45, Folder 7)
    - Individual Files: To (Box 45, Folder 8)
    - Individual Files: To (Box 45, Folder 9)
    - Individual Files: To (Box 45, Folder 10)
    - Individual Files: To, 1956 (Box 45, Folder 11)
    - Individual Files: Tr (Box 45, Folder 12)
    - Individual Files: Tu, 1959 (Box 45, Folder 13)
    - Individual Files: 1-U to 3-U (Box 45, Folder 14)
      Code: 1U-3U
    - Individual Files: Un, 1976 (Box 45, Folder 15)
    - Individual Files: 2-V to 12-V (Box 45, Folder 16)
      Code: 2V-12V
    - Individual Files: Vi, 1962 (Box 45, Folder 17)
    - Individual Files: Vi, 1957 (Box 45, Folder 18)
    - Individual Files: Vo, 1962 (Box 45, Folder 19)
    - Individual Files: 3-W to 29-W (Box 45, Folder 20)
      Code: 3W-29W
    - Individual Files: 30-W to 49-W (Box 45, Folder 21)
      Code: 30W-49W
    - Individual Files: Wa, 1978 (Box 45, Folder 22)
    - Individual Files: Wa (Box 45, Folder 23)
    - Individual Files: Wa (Box 45, Folder 24)
    - Individual Files: Wa (Box 45, Folder 25)
    - Individual Files: Wa, 1958 (Box 45, Folder 26)
    - Individual Files: Wa (Box 45, Folder 27)
    - Individual Files: Wa, 1964 (Box 45, Folder 28)
    - Individual Files: Wa (Box 45, Folder 29)
    - Individual Files: We (Box 45, Folder 30)
    - Individual Files: We (Box 45, Folder 31)
    - Individual Files: We (Box 45, Folder 32)
    - Individual Files: We, 1953 (Box 45, Folder 33)
    - Individual Files: We, 1977 (Box 45, Folder 34)
    - Individual Files: We (Box 45, Folder 35)
    - Individual Files: Wh (Box 45, Folder 36)
    - Individual Files: Wi, 1958 (Box 45, Folder 37)
    - Individual Files: Wi, 1959 (Box 45, Folder 38)
    - Individual Files: Wi, 1958 (Box 45, Folder 39)
    - Individual Files: Wi (Box 45, Folder 40)
    - Individual Files: Wi (Box 45, Folder 41)
    - Individual Files: Wi (Box 45, Folder 42)
    - Individual Files: Wi (Box 45, Folder 43)
      Code: 43W
    - Individual Files: Wi, 1976 (Box 45, Folder 44)
    - Individual Files: Wo (Box 45, Folder 45)
    - Individual Files: Wo, 1972 (Box 45, Folder 46)
    - Individual Files: Wo (Box 45, Folder 47)
    - Individual Files: Ye, 1956 (Box 45, Folder 48)
    - Individual Files: Yo, 1958 (Box 45, Folder 49)
    - Individual Files: Yo (Box 45, Folder 50)
    - Individual Files: Za, 1960 (Box 45, Folder 51)
    - Individual Files: Zi, 1959 (Box 45, Folder 52)
      Code:1Z
    - Individual Files: Zi (Box 45, Folder 53)
    - Individual Files: Zi, 1959 (Box 45, Folder 54)
      Code: 3Z
    - Individual Files: Zu, 1967 (Box 45, Folder 55)
    - Frazier Score Distributions (Box 45, Folder 56)
- Series II: Sample Tests
  - Sub-Series A: Blank Samples
    - Adams-Lepley: The Personal Audit, Form LL, 1945 (Box 46, Folder 1)
      Blank question form and manual of directions.
    - Allen: Providence Inventory Test in Music, Form A, 1932 (Box 46, Folder 2)
      For grades 4-9. Blank question form only.
    - Allport: The A-S Reaction Study, Form for Men and Form for Women, 1928-1939 (Box 46, Folder 3)
      Blank question forms and manual of directions.
    - Allport: A Study of Values, 1951 (Box 46, Folder 4)
      A Scale for Measuring the Dominant Interests in Personality. Blank question form, manual of directions, and score sheet.
    - American Council on Education: A. C. S. Cooperative Chemistry Test in Quantitative Analysis, Form X, 1947 (Box 46, Folder 5)
      Blank question form, manual of directions, right-answers key, and final percentage tables.
    - American Council on Education: A. C. S. Cooperative General Chemistry Test, Form 1946 (Box 46, Folder 6)
      For college students. Blank question form, manual of directions, right-answers key, and tentative percentage tables.
    - American Council on Education: A. C. S. Cooperative Organic Chemistry Test, Form W, 1946 (Box 46, Folder 7)
      Blank question form, right- answers key, and final percentage tables.
    - American Council on Education: Cooperative Ancient History Test, Form 1937 (Box 46, Folder 8)
      Blank question form only.
    - American Council on Education: Cooperative Algebra Test, Revised Series, Form T, 1943 (Box 46, Folder 9)
      Elementary algebra through quadratics. Blank question form, blank answer sheet, manual of directions, right-answers key, and percentage tables.
    - American Council on Education: Cooperative American History Test, Revised Series, Form X, 1947 (Box 46, Folder 10)
      Blank question form, manual of directions, right-answers key, and percentage tables.
    - American Council on Education: Cooperative College Mathematics Test, Provisional, Form T, 1943 (Box 46, Folder 11)
      For first-year courses. Blank question form, manual of directions, and percentage tables.
    - American Council on Education: Cooperative Commercial Arthmetic Test, Form X, 1947 (Box 46, Folder 12)
    - American Council on Education: Cooperative English Test, Form O, 1938 (Box 46, Folder 13)
      Usage, spelling, and vocabulary. Blank question form, manual of directions, and percentage tables.
    - American Council on Education: Cooperative English Test, Form R, Test A, Mechanics of Expression, 1941 (Box 46, Folder 14)
    - American Council on Education: Cooperative English Test, Form T, Test B1, Effectiveness of Expression, 1943 (Box 46, Folder 15)
      Lower level. Blank question form only
    - American Council on Education: Cooperative English Test, Form T, 1943 (Box 46, Folder 16)
      Higher level. Blank question form, blank answer sheet, manual of directions, right-answers key, and percentage tables.
    - American Council on Education: Cooperative French Test, Revised Series, Form N, 1937 (Box 46, Folder 17)
      Advanced. Blank question form only.
    - American Council on Education: Cooperative General Achievement Test, Form N and Form O, 1938 (Box 46, Folder 18)
      Part I: A Survey Test in the Social Studies. Part II: A Survey Test in the Natural Sciences. Part III: A Survey Test in Mathematics. Blank question forms and percentage tables.
    - American Council on Education: Cooperative General Culture Test, Form 1937 (Box 46, Folder 19)
    - American Council on Education: Cooperative General Culture Test, Revised Series, Form T, 1943 (Box 46, Folder 20)
      A revision of Form Q. Blank question form and percentage tables.
    - American Council on Education: Cooperative General Culture Test, Revised Series, Form W, 1946 (Box 46, Folder 21)
    - American Council on Education: Cooperative General Culture Test, Revised Series, Form X, 1947 (Box 46, Folder 22)
      Blank question form, manual of directions, and right-answers key.
    - American Council on Education: Cooperative Geology Test, Physical Geology, Form R, 1941 (Box 46, Folder 23)
      Blank question form, manual of directions, and percentage tables.
    - American Council on Education: Cooperative German Reading Scales, Scale A, Division 2, 1927 (Box 46, Folder 24)
      For second and third year German. Blank question form only.
    - American Council on Education: Cooperative Intermediate Algebra Test, Form T, 1943 (Box 46, Folder 25)
      Quadratics and beyond. Blank question form, blank answer sheet, manual of directions, right-answers key, and percentage tables.
    - American Council on Education: Cooperative Latin Test, Revised Series, Elementary Form N, 1937 (Box 46, Folder 26)
    - American Council on Education: Cooperative Literacy Acquaintance Test, Form 1937 (Box 46, Folder 27)
    - American Council on Education: Cooperative Literacy Acquaintance Test, Form O, 1938 (Box 46, Folder 28)
    - American Council on Education: Cooperative Literary Comprehension and Appreciation Test, Provisional Form R, 1941 (Box 46, Folder 29)
      Blank question form, blank answer sheet, manual of directions, and percentage tables.
    - American Council on Education: Cooperative Mathematics Pre-Test for College Students, Form X, 1947 (Box 46, Folder 30)
    - American Council on Education: Cooperative Plane Geometry Test, Revised Edition, Form T, 1943 (Box 46, Folder 31)
      Blank question form, blank answer sheet, manual of directions, right-answers key, and percentage tables.
    - American Council on Education: Cooperative Physics Test, Form 1937 (Box 46, Folder 32)
    - American Council on Education: Cooperative Solid Geometry Test, Revised Series, Form O, 1938 (Box 46, Folder 33)
      Blank question form, blank answer sheet, and percentage tables.
    - American Council on Education: Cooperative Trigonometry Test, Revised Edition, Form O, 1938 (Box 46, Folder 34)
    - American Council on Education: Cooperative World History Test, Revised Edition, Form X, 1947 (Box 46, Folder 35)
    - American Council on Education: Personality Report, Revision B, 1929 (Box 46, Folder 36)
      Blank report form.
    - American Council on Education: Psychological Examination for High School Students, 1946-1953 (Box 46, Folder 37)
      Blank question form, blank answer sheet, manual of directions, right-answers key, blank class record form, and percentage tables.
    - American Council on Education: Psychological Examination for College Freshmen, 1949 (Box 46, Folder 38)
    - Barrett-Ryan-Schrammel English Test, Form AM, 1938 (Box 46, Folder 39)
      For grades 9 to 12 and college. Blank question form, manual of directions, right-answers key, and blank class record form.
    - Bell Adjustment Inventory, Adult Form, 1938 (Box 46, Folder 40)
    - Bell Adjustment Inventory, Student Form (Box 46, Folder 41)
      For high school and college students. Manual of directions and right-answers key.
    - Bellak: Thematic Apperception Test, 1957 (Box 46, Folder 42)
      Interpretation guide.
    - Bennett-Gelink Short Employment Tests, Forms CA-2, CA-3, N-2, N-3, V-2, and V-3, 1951-1953 (Box 46, Folder 43)
      Blank question forms, manual of directions, and right-answers key.
    - Bernrueter: The Personality Inventory, 1935-1938 (Box 46, Folder 44)
      Blank question form, manual of directions, right- answers key, and percentage tables. This test includes six different right-answer keys for the same set of questions. All six are used for each person completing the test.
    - Bernrueter: The Personality Inventory, Maria's Method (Box 46, Folder 45)
      Includes much the same material as the previous folder, but also includes handwritten notes and other material.
    - Blackstone Stenographic Proficiency Tests, Form A, 1932 (Box 46, Folder 46)
    - Brown Personality Inventory (Box 46, Folder 47)
      Suggestions With Regard to Use and Interpretation of the Brown Personality Inventory.
    - Brown University Psychological Examination, Practice Exercises D, E, and F (Box 46, Folder 48)
    - Brown-Holtzman: Survey of Study Habits and Attitudes, 1953 (Box 46, Folder 49)
      Blank question form, blank answer sheet, manual of directions, right-answers key (Female), right-answers key (Male), elimination key (Female), elimination key (Male), counseling key (Female), and counseling key (Male)
    - Bruce: Business Judgment Test, 1953 (Box 46, Folder 50)
    - Bruce: Sales Comprehension Test, Form M, 1953-1954 (Box 46, Folder 51)
    - Bruce: Sales Motivation Inventory, Form A, 1953-1965 (Box 46, Folder 52)
    - Bruce: Supervisory Practices Test, 1957 (Box 46, Folder 53)
      Blank question form, manual of directions, and right-answers key. No biographical data has been entered on the question form, but the questions have been answered.
    - Bruce: Test of Sales Aptitute, Form A, 1947-1952 (Box 46, Folder 54)
    - Byron Harless & Associates, Memo to Employers (no.1), 1967 (Box 46, Folder 55)
      April, 1967. Government Regulations and Employment Testing.
    - California Achievement Test, Questions and Answers, 1961 (Box 46, Folder 56)
      Prepared by the Research and Development staff of the California Test Bureau.
    - California Progressive Tests in Social and Related Sciences, Elementary Battery, Form A, 1947 (Box 46, Folder 57)
      Blank question forms, manual of directions, right-answers key, and blank class record. Tests included: Part I, Social Studies I (The American Heritage; People of Other Lands and Times); Part II, Social Studies II (Basic Social Processes); and Par
    - California Reading Test, Elementary, Form W, 1957-1963 (Box 46, Folder 58)
      For grades 4-6. Blank question form, blank answer sheet, manual of directions, right-answers key, blank class record form, and percentage tables.
    - California Reading Test, Junior High Level, Form W, 1957-1963 (Box 46, Folder 59)
      For grades 7-9. Blank question form, blank answer sheet, manual of directions, right-answers key, blank class record form, and percentage tables.
    - California Short-Form Test of Mental Maturity, Advanced, Form S, 1957 (Box 46, Folder 60)
      For grades 10 to Adult. Blank question form, blank answer sheet, manual of directions, right-answers key, and blank class record form. Also includes several answer sheets that have been filled out.
    - New California Short-Form Tet of Mental Maturity, Intermediate, Form S, 1947 (Box 46, Folder 61)
      For grades 7-10. Blank question form only.
    - California Test of Mental Maturity, Level 2, 1963 (Box 46, Folder 62)
      For grades 4-6. Includes manual of directions only.
    - California Test of Mental Maturity, Intermediate, 1951 (Box 46, Folder 63)
      For grades 7-10 and Adult. Blank question form, manual of directions, and right-answers key.
    - California Test of Mental Maturity, Advanced Series, 1946 (Box 46, Folder 64)
      For grades 9 to Adult. Blank question form, manual of directions, right-answers key, and blank class record form. Also includes one answer sheet that has been filled out.
    - California Test of Personality, Primary Series, Form A, 1942 (Box 46, Folder 65)
      Kindergarten to grade 3. Blank question form, manual of directions, right-answers key, and blank class record form.
    - California Test of Personality, Elementary Series, Form A, 1942 (Box 46, Folder 66)
      For grades 4-9. Blank question form, manual of directions, right-answers key, and blank class record form.
    - California Test of Personality, Intermediate Series, Form A, 1942 (Box 46, Folder 67)
      For grades 7-10. Blank question form, manual of directions, right-answers key, and blank class record form.
    - California Test of Personality, Secondary Series, Form A, 1942 (Box 46, Folder 68)
      For grades 9-14. Blank question form, manual of directions, right-answers key, and blank class record form.
    - California Test of Personality, Adult Series, Form A, 1942 (Box 46, Folder 69)
      Blank question form, manual of directions, right-answers key, and blank class record form.
    - Cardall: Practical Judgment Test, 1949 (Box 46, Folder 70)
      Article "A Note on the Cardall Practical Judgment Test" by Dorothy H. Carrington. Reprinted for Journal of Applied Psychology, v.33:no.1 (1949: Feb.).
    - Cardall: Primary Business Interest Test, 1942 (Box 46, Folder 71)
    - Cattell: Sixteen Personality Factor Questionnaire, Forms A and B, 1951-1964 (Box 46, Folder 72)
      The 16 P. F. Test. Blank question form, blank answer sheet, manual of directions, scoring key, and blank profile form.
    - Civil Service: Junior Scientist and Engineer Examination, AN 3546, 1949 (Box 46, Folder 73)
      Sample questions.
    - Civil Service: Student Nurse, AN 3547, 1949 (Box 46, Folder 74)
    - Civil Service: Substitute Railway Postal Clerk Examination, AN 3530, 1947 (Box 46, Folder 75)
    - Civil Service: Telephone Operator, AN 3529, 1947 (Box 46, Folder 76)
    - Civil Service: Sample Questions, 1948-1949 (Box 46, Folder 77)
      Includes AN 3536 (August 1948); AN 3510 (July 1949).
    - Cleeton: Vocational Interest Inventory, Form A, 1942 (Box 46, Folder 78)
      Blank question form (Women), blank question form (Men), and manual of directions.
    - Cochrane: Number Fact Check Sheet, Forms A, 1947 (Box 46, Folder 79)
      Blank question form and manual of directions
    - Columbia Research Bureau Aural French Test, Form A, 1930 (Box 46, Folder 80)
    - Consultation Service (Box 46, Folder 81)
      Blank registration form and blank questionnaire.
    - The Cooperative English Test, 1960 (Box 46, Folder 82)
      Advertising brochure.
    - Cooperative English Test, Test CI, Reading Comprehension, Form Y, 1948 (Box 46, Folder 83)
      Lower level, grades 7-12. Blank question form only.
    - Cooperative School and College Ability Test (SCAT), Technical Report, 1957 (Box 46, Folder 84)
      Report only.
    - Cooperative School and College Ability Test (SCAT), Manual for Interpreting Scores, 1957 (Box 46, Folder 85)
      Manual of directions and scoring key.
    - Cooperative SCAT-STEP Supplement, 1958 (Box 46, Folder 86)
    - Cooperative School and College Ability Test (SCAT), Forms 1A, 2A, 3A, 4A, and 5A, 1955-1957 (Box 46, Folder 87)
    - Cooperative School and College Ability Test (SCAT), Forms 1A, 2A, 3A, 4A, and 5A (Box 46, Folder 88)
      Blank answer sheets and right-answers key.
    - Cornehlsen: Sentence Completion Test (Box 47, Folder 1)
    - Cornehlsen: Sentence Completion Test, 1958 (Box 47, Folder 2)
    - Cowan Adolescent Personality Schedule (Box 47, Folder 3)
      Revision no.2. Blank question form only.
    - Coxe-Orleans Prognosis Test of Taching Ability, Form A, 1930 (Box 47, Folder 4)
    - Crawford Spatial Relations Test (Box 47, Folder 5)
    - Cross English Test, Form B, 1923 (Box 47, Folder 6)
      For high school and colleges. Blank question form only.
    - Department of Labor: GAB, Book 1, 1946 (Box 47, Folder 7)
    - Detroit Advanced Intelligence Test, Form W, 1925-1940 (Box 47, Folder 8)
      for high school and colleges. Blank question form and manual of directions.
    - Detroit Alpha Intelligence Test, Form M, 1924 (Box 47, Folder 9)
      For grades 5-9. Blank question form only
    - Detroit Alpha Intelligence Test, Form S, 1940 (Box 47, Folder 10)
      For grades 4-8. Blank question form, manual of directions, mental age norms, and blank class record form.
    - Detroit Mechanical Aptitude Examination for Boys, 1928 (Box 47, Folder 11)
    - Detroit Mechanical Aptitude Examination for Girls, 1928 (Box 47, Folder 12)
    - Diagnostic Test of Achievement in Music (Box 47, Folder 13)
    - Diagnostic Test in American History, Series 2B, 1920 (Box 47, Folder 14)